(Sheldon:)Have you suffered
a recent blow to the head?
Hey, you don't have to be so mean.
I'm sorry. Have you suffered
a recent blow to the head?
(Penny:)No. You just suck at teaching.
(Sheldon:)Really? Of those two explanations,
which one seems the most likely?
(Penny:)Oh, God.
(Penny:)Sheldon, look, I'm trying to understand
but you're going too fast.
(Penny:)-Can you just back up a little bit?
-All right.
(Sheldon:)It's a warm summer evening
in ancient Greece--
(Penny:)Not that far back.
Okay, at what point
did you begin to feel lost?
(Penny:)I don't know. Where were we looking up
at the night sky?
(Sheldon:)-Greece.
-Damn it.
(Penny:)Look,
there's no need to get frustrated.
(Sheldon:)People learn at different rates.
(Sheldon:)Unlike objects falling in a vacuum,
which...?
(Sheldon:)MA equals MG...?
(Penny:)-Squared?
-No.